<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cache Mode on UAsset Browser</title>
    <link>/docs/cachemode/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cache Mode on UAsset Browser</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{year} Mary Nate, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 10:10:56 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/docs/cachemode/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>What is Cache Mode</title>
        <link>/docs/cachemode/whatiscachemode/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/docs/cachemode/whatiscachemode/</guid>
        <description>What is Cache Mode When UAsset Browser is opened, the folders/assets data will be gathered right away and saved in memory for displaying/validating/importing. The gathering process time is highly depending on the files number and the hardware performance.
folder gathering
asset gathering
While swithcing to Cahce Mode, the processed folders/assets data will be stored in one cache database file, and can be serialized into memory as requested, and skip the time consuming gathering step.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Enter and Exit Cache Mode</title>
        <link>/docs/cachemode/enterexitcachemode/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/docs/cachemode/enterexitcachemode/</guid>
        <description>Enter Cache Mode There&amp;rsquo;re 2 ways to enter Cache Mode:
1. Save and Switch to Cache Mode 2. Switch to Cache Mode (Without saving) </description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Switch Cache Database File</title>
        <link>/docs/cachemode/switchcachefile/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/docs/cachemode/switchcachefile/</guid>
        <description>Switch Cache Database File The defualt cache database file will be saved in current project&amp;rsquo;s Save folder with the file name UAssetBrowser.cachedb.
You can type in cache file name directly in the cache file input text box (on bottom of Asset View) to change cache database file.
If the input file is not exist, new file with the same path will be created automatically with current cached folders/assets data.
Or you can click the &amp;hellip; button beside the file path to choose an existing cache dabase file in the file choose dialog.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Rescan Revalidate Reparse</title>
        <link>/docs/cachemode/rescanvalidateparse/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/docs/cachemode/rescanvalidateparse/</guid>
        <description>When in cache mode, folders/assets data are fetched from a cache database instead of folders/assets from file system. So it might getting out of sync when the folders/assets changed. There&amp;rsquo;re functionalities built in UAsset Browser to help resolving the outdated data issue without re-created the cache database from scratch.
Rescan To make sure folders data up to date, you can right click a folder to Rescan current selected folder recursively.</description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>